Statehood Commission
DC Public Library, Special Collections
- Series 4: Topics, 1788, 1941, 1968, 1980-1993
  - Strategic Plan, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Plan, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Survey on Statehood - Post, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee plan "Shadow Delegates" - 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - "The Transition from a Capital City to a Model State", Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Transition team reports, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Washington Lawyers' Committee, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Visiting Nurse Association, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Voters Guide, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Voter participatory education, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Voting rights, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Waiving residency requirement for teachers, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - "Washington View" Volume 3 #1, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - World dialogue on disarmament and detente, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Zoning, 1980s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Zoning, 1980s (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Legislative Matters, 1986-1994
  - H.R. 51, 1987, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 51 - Activities, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 51 - Activities, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 51, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 51 - Amendments, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 51 - Background materials, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - H.R. Briefing book, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book drafts, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book drafts, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book originals/appendices, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book appendices, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book cover insert, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book foreward and table of contents, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book inside book pocket, Undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book issues, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - H.R. 51 - Briefing book originals/statement, Undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 51 - Brief book synopsis, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 51 - Congressional Budget Office report, June 29 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 51 - Constitution, Undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 51 - House District Committee Internal Memoranda, Undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 51 - Executive Summary of by Republican Study Committee, September 4 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 51 - Section by section outline, Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 51 - Statement opposition - Thomas J. Bliley Jr., May 20 1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 51 - Strategy for the Passage of, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 51 - Testimony Before House Committee on the District of Columbia - Stephen Markman, April 17 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - House Committee on the District - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs, May 5 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - House Committee on the District - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs, May 28 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - House Committee on the District - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs - opening statement of Run Dellums, April 30 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - House Committee on the District - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs - opening statement of Walter Fauntroy, April 30 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - House Committee on the District - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs - opening remarks by Stan Parris, May 19 1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 51 - Markup - Response to Issues raised by Representative Walter Fauntroy, May 20 1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 51 - Oversight hearing - opening statements of Walter Fauntroy, March 26 1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - H.R. 52, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - H.R. 325, Undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - H.R. 1629 - Bill to adopt Statehood Constitution, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 3861 - Bill to provide for Admission of the State of New Columbia, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - H.R. 4718 - D.C. Statehood Bill Background paper, June 1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - H.R. 4776 - Conference report, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - S898 - A Bill to Provide for the Admission of the State of New Columbia, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - S1118 - A Bill to Provide Mayor, City council and Nonvoting delegate, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Bills and Acts for Other States Admission, 1802-1911 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Bills and Acts for Other States Admission, 1802-1911 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bills and Acts for Other States Admission, 1802-1911 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - CRS report for Congress - shadow representatives in Congress, June 16 1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Congressional activity for statehood, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Congressional activity for statehood -January-March, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Enabling Acts - Acts of Administration Memorandum, February 4 1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Congressional record: Implications for Congress of Rising District of Columbia Debt, March 31 1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Congressional record - statehood legislation, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Congressional welcome from Statehood Party, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Constitution of the U.S. - analysis and interpretation, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Act 7-19 - Constitution of New Columbia, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Appropriations Act - Conference report to accompany - H.J. Research 738, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - D.C. appropriations bills, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - D.C. appropriations bill FY 1988 - Corporation Counsel Legal Advice Memoranda, January 13 1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - D.C. appropriations bill FY 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - D.C. appropriations bill FY 1990 - continuing resolution (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - D.C. City Council Rules, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - D.C. City Council - FY 1987 budget request (Bill 6-376) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - D.C. City Council - Parental Responsibility Act - Bill 1-278 background, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Jesse Helms - letter against statement, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - House hearing on boundaries of State of New Columbia - Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health, March 17 1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - House hearing on Constitution of the State of New Columbia - Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health, March 26 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - House hearings on transferring law enforcement and judicial authority - Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health, April 7 1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - House hearings - FY 1987 budget, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - House hearing - District Committee [re: economic issues], September 30 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - House of representatives list, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Legislative issues, 1987-1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Legislative materials, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Legislative materials, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Legislative materials, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Legislative materials, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Congress re statehood, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lobbying report forms, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - New Columbia Constitution, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - New Columbia Omnibus Act, Undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - New Columbia Omnibus Act - example, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Statehood hearing invitations, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Statehood supporters - senate, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Statement by Jo Butler on Commission budget, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Statement by Jo Butler and Arrington Dixon on Commission budget, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Statement by Jo Butler and Arrington Dixon on Commission budget, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Testimony before D.C. City Council - Jo Butler, March 30 1987 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Testimony before City Council - Jo Butler and Arrington Dixon - FY 188-1989 budgets, February 21 1989 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Testimony before City Council - Jo Butler and Arrington Dixon - FY 188-1989 budgets (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Testimony before City Council - Committee on Self Determination, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Testimony before City Council - D.C. pretrial services (PR 7-288), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Testimony before D.C. City Council - Arrington Dixon, March 17 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Testimony before D.C. City Council - FY 1995 supplemental budget request - Ned Sloan, November 29 1994 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Testimony before D.C. City Council - No taxation without representation research of 1993 (PR10-26) - Ned Sloan, June 16 1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Testimony before House Committee on the District of Columbia - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Andrew F. Brimmer, September 30 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Testimony before House Committee on the District of Columbia - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Cheryl Long, March 17 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Testimony before House Committee on the District of Columbia - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Jason Il Newman, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Testimony before House Committee on the District of Columbia - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Matthew Watson, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Testimony for statehood, Undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Testimony before the Senate Committee on Government Affairs - Jesse Jackson, August 4 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Testimony before the Senate Committee on Government Affairs - Dr. Alan Lessoff, August 4 1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Testimony regarding H.R. 2482 - House Committee on D.C - Judiciary and Education Subcommittee - Jo Butler, November 14 1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Testimony regarding economics of statehood - House Committee on D.C. - Robert D. Ebel, September 30 1986. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Marion Barry, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - David Clarke, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - James Dyke, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Walter Fauntroy - opening statement, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Senator Edward M.Kennedy, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Wilhemina Rolark, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Testimony supporting statehood before House Committee on D.C. - Subcommittee on Fiscal Affairs and Health - Charles Ruff, March 26 1987 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Write in Votes, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Series 6: Clippings and Press Releases, 1978--1987
  - Clippings, 1978-1987 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1987-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Series 7: Public Relations, 1987-1993
  - Apter and Associates - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Apter and Associates - General, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Apter and Associates - General, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Apter and Associates - Press reports, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Apter and Associates - Press reports, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Public Schools Teachers Convention Workshop Catalog, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - Press package, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - Press releases, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - Rally, December 1 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition - Supporter letter, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Editorials, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Editorials, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - "Facts You May Not Know About D.C. and Statehood", 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Fact sheets and outreach materials, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - "Fifty Stars" slide show, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - "Fifty-one Stars: A Test", Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Frequently Asked Questions Regarding Statehood Economic Issues, Undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Government-elect transition teams model reports, September 27 1988 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 51 - public relations materials, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - HR. 51 - public relations plan, June 14 1988 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 51 publicity, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 4718 - D.C. Statehood bill background paper, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Jones, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Letters to the editor, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Letters to the editor, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Liberty Bell Train, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Media contacts, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Media reports on statehood, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Media reports on statehood, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Media reports on statehood, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Media reports on statehood, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Memorial day tribute - PR announcements, May 30 1987 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - "New Columbia: 51st State of the Union" - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "New Columbia: 51st State of the Union" - Maguire-Reeder Award, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "New Columbia: 51st State of the Union" - Speakers kit, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "New Columbia: 51st State of the Union" - U.S. Festivals Association, June 20 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - New Columbia Video, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - New Columbia Video, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - One Month Daily Curriculum - National Rainbow Coalition for D.C. Statehood Campaign, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Opinion survey forms - complete no's (sampled selection), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Opinion survey forms - completed yes (sampled selection), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Opinion survey forms - returned with letters, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Opinion survey forms - unsure (sampled selection), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Republican Study Committee report on statement, September 4 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Poll results, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Press packets - Democratic national Convention, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Press releases, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Program of work, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Public education, Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Public education - correspondence, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Public education - activities for statehood, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Public relations program, March 19 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Public relations program, July 3 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Public relations program, May 6 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Public relations program for Democratic and Republican national conventions, May 19 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Public relations reports, May 1987 -November 1988 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Public relations report, January 7-21 1988 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Public relations reports, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Publicity materials, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Publicity packet, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Publicity packets, Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Public support plea, May 19 1989 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Radio and T.V. Reports, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Radio and T.V. Reports, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Statehood Coalition publicity materials, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "Statehood for the District: A Summary", Undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Statehood solicitation letter, November 21 1989 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Strategy for Passage of D.C. Statehood Legislation, January 31 1989 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Survey, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Teaching guide, Undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Teacher training workshop, March 14 1987 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Timetable for future public relations activities for statehood, May-19June 1982 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - "Twenty-Five Bills of Importance to the Education of African-American Students", Undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - "The Unfinished Agenda of the U.S. Constitution Workshop", March 14 1987 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - "Updates" and "Action News", Undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Vote Yes For D.C. Statehood, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - What is the Statehood/Compact Commission, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Series 8: Research, 1948-1993
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Alaska Congressional Materials, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Alaska Omnibus Act, June 1986 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Alaska research, 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Alaska research, 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Alaska research, 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Alaska research, 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Alaska research, 1950-1958 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Alaska research/reports/letters, 1951-1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Alaska - Proposed Organization of the Executive Branch- Public Administration Service, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Alaska - Proposed Organization of the Executive Branch- Public Administration Service, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Alaska - Proposed Organization of the Executive Branch- Public Administration Service, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Alaska - Proposed Organization of the Executive Branch- Public Administration Service, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Alaska - State of Alaska v. US, July 28 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Alaska transition and reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Alaska transition and reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Alaska transition and reorganization, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Alaska transition and reorganization, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Arizona and New Mexico statehood materials, 1910-1911 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Compact Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Compact Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Compact Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia, 1975-1987 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia, 1975-1987 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia, 1975-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia, 1975-1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Embassy issue research, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Financial research, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Financial research, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Financial research, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Financial research, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - General services, Undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - General services, Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - General services, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - General services, Undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - General services, Undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii research, 1950-1955, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii research, 1950-1955, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii research, 1950-1955, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Hawaii state government reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Hawaii state government reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1981 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii state government reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii state government reorganization (non-inclusive), 1959-1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii Omnibus Act, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Legal research options, November 6 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rico statehood research memoranda, September 19 1988 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Puerto Rico statehood research memoranda, October 3 1988 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Puerto Rico - research material - general, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Statehood, 1953-1987 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Statehood, 1953-1987 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Statehood, 1953-1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Statehood, 1953-1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - State statistics information, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Series 9: Correspondence, 1987-1994
  - ANC Commissioner letter, April 20 1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Butler-Boland letter, September 25 1989 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Butler-Fauntroy statehood mission teach letters, January 30 1987 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Butler-Smith letter re budget, February 21 1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Community leader letter, May 19 1989 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Dear Friend letter, July 28 1989 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Dear Friend letter, November 15 1989 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Election follow-up memoranda, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Fauntroy-Mason letter, January 17 1989 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Maguire-Reeder letter, October 18 1989 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Mazzoli - Representative Romano L. letter and background, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Non-voting representative letter (J. Jackson and C. Moreland), January 9 1991 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Rimensnyder letter, November 21 1989 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - School Without Walls letter, September 20 1989 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Spock letter, June 8 1987 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Columbia Statehood Constitutional convention, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to Congress, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence with Controller, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, February-March 1994 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to Congress, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 29)